{
  "LevelId": 65,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 661,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BENCHMARK",
      "question": "standard or point of reference that is used for comparison or evaluation,"
    },
    {
      "id": 662,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "GOGGLEBOX",
      "question": "British television show where people watch and comment on various television"
    },
    {
      "id": 663,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AVOCADOES",
      "question": "creamy fruits that are often associated with dishes like guacamole"
    },
    {
      "id": 664,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "ARCHRIVAL",
      "question": "individual's main competitor or adversary, often regarded with intense rivalry"
    },
    {
      "id": 665,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BEESWINGS",
      "question": "delicate, translucent wing covers left behind by honeybees"
    },
    {
      "id": 666,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "ABOLITION",
      "question": "the act of officially ending or eliminating a system, practice,"
    },
    {
      "id": 667,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BACKSTAIR",
      "question": "a private or secondary staircase, typically located in the rear or less visible part of a building"
    },
    {
      "id": 668,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "APPLIANCE",
      "question": "term for a device or machine designed for a specific task,"
    },
    {
      "id": 669,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AIRDROMES",
      "question": "facilities equipped for the takeoff, landing, and maintenance of aircraft,"
    },
    {
      "id": 670,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "ALONENESS",
      "question": "express the state of being entirely alone or experiencing solitude"
    },
    {
      "id": 671,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "MEDITATION",
      "question": "often through breathing exercises or mindful contemplation,"
    }
  ]
}